<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Las Vegas Guide</string>
    <string name="title">Open with</string>

    <string-array name="sightName">
        <item>Paris Hotel and Eiffel Tower</item>
        <item>Bellagio</item>
        <item>Caesar’s Palace</item>
        <item>Mandalay Bay</item>
        <item>Mirage Hotel: Secret Garden</item>
        <item>Hershey’s chocolate world</item>
        <item>Fremont Street</item>
        <item>Ancient Egypt</item>
        <item>New York - New York</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sightAddress">
        <item>3655 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3600 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3570 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3950 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3400 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3790 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>Fremont Street</item>
        <item>3900 South Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3790 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sightDescription">
        <item> Forty-six stories above the city streets, the Eiffel Tower Experience is an observation deck with incredible 360-degree views.
            Out front is a scale model of the Eiffel Tower, and down the way is a recreation of the Paris Opera House.
           </item>
        <item>The Bellagio Resort is a high-end hotel complex, with a wide variety of attractions.
            The most impressive and famous feature is the fountain show.
            In front of the Bellagio, the dancing fountains perform a beautiful display of water set to music.
            From the sidewalk, visitors have a ringside view. This is often described as the best free attraction in Las Vegas.</item>
        <item>Currently Caesar’s Palace is a massive complex, complete with every imaginable entertainment option.
            The hotel is closely associated with shows held in its huge concert venue known as "The Colosseum".
            Top performers (which have included Celine Dion and Elton John) perform here for extended periods, and shows are often booked out well in advance.</item>
        <item>One of the key highlights at Mandalay Bay Resort complex is the Shark Reef Aquarium. The massive 1,300,000-gallon tank holds a wide variety of sharks, fish, rays, reptiles, and marine invertebrates.
            About 100 sharks from 15 different species and more than 2,000 animals in all are on display.
            The Shark Tunnel is the most impressive feature.</item>
        <item>In front of the Mirage Casino Resort is a volcano, which erupts at regular intervals.
            At night, the glowing red fire shooting out is one of the most unique sites visible from the sidewalk.
            Inside the Mirage is the Secret Garden and Dolphin Habitat.
            You can see a wide variety of exotic animals, including white lions.</item>
        <item>Stop by Hershey’s chocolate world Las Vegas to see a famous American icon in chocolate.
            The store features a sculpture of the Statue of Liberty made out of almost 800 lbs. of HERSHEY’s Milk Chocolate.
            Stop by the store to customize your very own chocolate bars, choose from a wide selection of tasty treats, and shop for your favourite HERSHEY’S gifts.
            It is sure to be a unique and unforgettable shopping experience!</item>
        <item>In old downtown Las Vegas,
            Fremont Street is a pedestrian-only area with all kinds of unique sites.
            A five-block section of Fremont Street is covered over with a canopy of LED lights that illuminate the sky in a spectacle of different colors and designs as you walk below.
            Each night a fantastic music and visual show takes place overhead.
            Street performers and special entertainment acts often perform in this area.
            P.S Do not forget your wallet because you would like to leave some tips.</item>
        <item>Designed in an ancient Egyptian theme, the hotel is shaped like a pyramid, with a sphinx proudly gazing out over the street.
            The Luxor, like all the major resorts, offers a wide variety of restaurants and shopping opportunities.
            One of the standout features of this hotel is the beam of light that projects from the highest point of the pyramid and shoots up into the night sky.
            It can be seen from throughout Las Vegas. </item>
        <item>From live music on the Brooklyn Bridge to rowdy evenings around dueling pianos, you’re sure to find something for the whole family!
            And with 84,000 square of feet of casino space,
            there are more than 67 table games and hundreds of slot machines to entertain the novice to the pro.
            Why not be a part of it all at New York-New York?</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="restaurants">
        <item>Black tap craft Burgers and Beer</item>
        <item>LAVO Itallian Restaurant</item>
        <item>Americana Restaurant</item>
        <item>The Boiling Crab</item>
        <item>Water Grill</item>
        <item>Chart House</item>
        <item>Honey Salt</item>
        <item>Abriya Raku</item>
        <item>SW Steakhouse</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="restaurantAddress">
        <item>3355 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3325 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>2620 Regatta Dr Suite 118</item>
        <item>4025 S Decatur Blvd</item>
        <item>3500 South Las Vegas Blvd Space #G01</item>
        <item>129 East Fremont St</item>
        <item>1031 S Rampart Blvd</item>
        <item>5030 Spring Mountain Rd</item>
        <item>3131 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cuisine">
    <item>American 🇺🇸, Steakhouse, Vegetarian </item>
        <item>Itallian 🇮🇹</item>
        <item>American 🇺🇸, Steakhouse, Vegetarian</item>
        <item>American 🇺🇸, Seafood</item>
        <item>Asian 🥢, Seafood</item>
        <item>Steakhouse, Seafood </item>
        <item>American 🇺🇸</item>
        <item>Chinese 🇨🇳, Japanese 🇯🇵</item>
        <item>American 🇺🇸, Steakhouse, Seafood</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="priceRange">
        <item>$ 20 - $ 45</item>
        <item>$ 31 - $ 60</item>
        <item>$ 31 - $ 60 </item>
        <item>$ 15 - $ 35</item>
        <item>$ 31 - $ 50</item>
        <item>$ 35 - $ 60</item>
        <item>$ 20 - $ 40</item>
        <item>$ 18 - $ 45</item>
        <item>$ 50 - $ 80</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="restaurantNumber">
        <item>+1 702-414-1000</item>
        <item>+1 702-791-1800</item>
        <item>+1 702-331-5565</item>
        <item>+1 702-386-0808</item>
        <item>+1 702-832-4777</item>
        <item>+1 702-386-8364</item>
        <item>+1 702-445-6100</item>
        <item>+1 702-367-3511</item>
        <item>+1 702-770-3325</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="restaurantWorkingHours">
        <item>12pm - 10pm</item>
        <item>6:30pm - 10:30pm</item>
        <item>12pm - 11:30pm</item>
        <item>12pm - 10pm</item>
        <item>11:30am - 10pm</item>
        <item>11am - 8pm</item>
        <item>11:30am - 9pm</item>
        <item>6pm - 3am</item>
        <item>5:30pm - 10pm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="museum">
        <item>Titanic: The Artifact Exhibition</item>
        <item>The ARIA Fine Art</item>
        <item>Madame Tussauds</item>
        <item>Real Bodies at Bally’s</item>
        <item>Marvel S.T.A.T.I.O.N</item>
        <item>Nevada State Museum</item>
        <item>The Neon Museum</item>
        <item>The House of selfies</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="museumDescription">
        <item>Unprecedented opportunity to travel back in time.
            Experience the wonder and tragedy of the world’s most famous ocean-liner, Titanic.
            Over 250 authentic artifacts recovered from the wreck site of Titanic, as well as extensive recreations of some of the most famous rooms from the Ship,
            make this an educational and entertaining experience perfect for all ages.</item>
        <item>The ARIA Fine Art Collection encompasses a multitude of styles and media—ranging from sculptures and
            paintings to large-scale installations—engaging visitors on a visual and intellectual level.</item>
        <item>Madame Tussauds displays more than 100 intricately designed replicas of well-known celebrities from the worlds of film, television and music.</item>
        <item>REAL BODIES at Bally’s uses real human specimens to explore the complex inner workings of the human form in a refreshing and thought-provoking style.</item>
        <item>Avengers S.T.A.T.I.O.N. Las Vegas is an immersive and educational experience that will bring you into the world of The Avengers.
            Welcoming all ages, visitors are granted access to the official S.T.A.T.I.O.N. headquarters and
            taken deep into the Marvel Cinematic Universe with access to an array of intelligence files,
            classified studies and experiments that explore the history and scientific origins of The Avengers.</item>
        <item>The Nevada State Museum engages diverse audiences in understanding and celebrating Nevada’s natural and cultural heritage..
             The museum presents heritage through unique and authentic educational experiences, enhanced by an environment of comfort, interaction, and inspiration.</item>
        <item>What’s one of the first things that pops into your head when you’re imagining Nevada? NEON.
            The Neon Museum is focuses solely on colleting, preserving,
            studying and exhibiting iconic Las Vegas signs for educational, historic, arts and cultural enrichment.</item>
        <item>It is the only form of photography many people care about, so of course there is a museum dedicated to it.
            The interactive attraction looks at the history of the self-photograph and, naturally, offers several new selfie ops, including a “Game of Thrones”-style throne assembled out of selfie sticks.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="museumAddress">
        <item>3900 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3730 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3377 S Las Vegas Blvd Ste. 2001</item>
        <item>3645 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3300 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>309 S Valley View Blvd</item>
        <item>770 Las Vegas Blvd N</item>
        <item>450 Fremont St Ste 251</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="museumWorkingHours">
        <item>10am – 9pm</item>
        <item>12pm – 12am</item>
        <item>11am – 5pm</item>
        <item>10am – 9pm</item>
        <item>11am - 5pm</item>
        <item>9am – 5pm</item>
        <item>10am - 10pm</item>
        <item>4pm - 10pm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fun">
        <item>Big shot</item>
        <item>X-Scream</item>
        <item>Gondola Rides</item>
        <item>SlotZilla Zipline</item>
        <item>Insanity</item>
        <item>Bungee Jumping</item>
        <item>High Roller Ferris</item>
        <item>Helicopter Rides</item>
        <item>The Big Apple Coaster</item>
        <item>Circus circus</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="funAddress">
        <item>2000 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>2000 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3355 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>425 Fremont St #160</item>
        <item>2000 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>2000 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>3545 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        <item>4511 W Cheyenne Ave #101</item>
        <item>3797 S Las Vegas Blvd New York-New York</item>
        <item>2880 S Las Vegas Blvd</item>
        </string-array>

    <string-array name="funWorkingHours">
        <item>12pm – 10pm</item>
        <item>12pm – 10pm</item>
        <item>10am – 11pm</item>
        <item>12pm – 1am</item>
        <item>12pm – 10pm</item>
        <item>12pm – 1am</item>
        <item>2pm – 12am</item>
        <item>8am – 1pm</item>
        <item>11am - 11pm</item>
        <item>24/7</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="funPrice">
        <item>$ 12</item>
        <item>$ 14</item>
        <item>$ 29</item>
        <item>$ 29</item>
        <item>$ 14</item>
        <item>$ 123.95</item>
        <item>$ 24.95</item>
        <item>$ 134</item>
        <item>$ 14</item>
        <item>$ 17.95</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>